

Tomas Fiers

Signals, Software, and Science.

tomas.fiers@gmail.com +32 478 13 43 26

Profile

Inquisitive mind, architectural skills, and mindful of the other person's experience (user, client, colleague) • Proven quantitative skills, particularly in machine learning and data analysis • High signal-to-noise communication • Toolbox: applied mathematics, software engineering, and a broad background knowledge in tech & science

Experience

<u>NERF</u> (imec - VIB - KU Leuven) - **Signal processing engineer in** neuroscience - **Master's thesis**

FEBRUARI 2017 - PRESENT, LEUVEN

Fluves - Business development intern

SEPTEMBER 2017 - DECEMBER 2017, GHENT

Byteflies - Signal processing intern

JULY 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017, ANTWERP

<u>Arenberg Symphony Orchestra</u> - President & section leader

2013 - 2016, LEUVEN

<u>DataCamp</u> - **Software engineering intern**

JULY 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2016, LEUVEN

VVW & Sport Vlaanderen - Sailing instructor

2010 - 2012, NIEUWPOORT, HEIST, HOFSTADE

Education

KU Leuven – MSc, burgerlijk ingenieur – Biomedical engineering 2016 – 2018

Electives in artificial intelligence & machine learning, advanced statistical methods for data-analysis, neuroscience, commercial law, and IT security.

KU Leuven - BSc, Computer science & Electrical engineering

2012 - 2016